[
  {
    "id": 1746971717774,
    "timestamp": "2025-05-11T13:55:17.774Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "question": "What is your first and last name?",
        "answer": "milena avagyan"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your date of birth? (mm/dd/yyyy)",
        "answer": "07/02/2003"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your ethnicity?",
        "answer": "Asian"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "answer": "Female"
      },
      {
        "question": "What country are you from?",
        "answer": "armenia"
      },
      {
        "question": "How satisfied were you with the product from 1 to 5 (5 = very satisfied)?",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you use the product for?",
        "answer": "skincare"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you like most about it?",
        "answer": "durability"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you not you like about it?",
        "answer": "scent"
      },
      {
        "question": "What would you improve or change?",
        "answer": "scent"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where were you when you used the product?",
        "answer": "at home"
      },
      {
        "question": "Was anyone else involved in the decision or experience?",
        "answer": "no"
      },
      {
        "question": "How did you first hear about this product?",
        "answer": "friend"
      }
    ],
    "analysis": "The interviewee's name is Milena Avagyan. She was born on July 2nd, 2003, which makes her currently around 17 or 18 years old. She identifies as Asian and female. She is originally from Armenia. She rated her satisfaction with a specific product with a 4 on a scale from 1 to 5, 5 being very satisfied. The product under discussion was used for skincare purposes. She enjoyed the durability of the product but was not pleased with the scent. In fact, she would improve or change the scent if given the choice. The product was utilized at home, and the purchase decision was made independently. She first heard about the product from a friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 1747007729668,
    "timestamp": "2025-05-11T23:55:29.668Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "question": "What is your first and last name?",
        "answer": "milena avagyan"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your date of birth? (mm/dd/yyyy)",
        "answer": "07/02/2003"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your ethnicity?",
        "answer": "Asian"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "answer": "Female"
      },
      {
        "question": "What country are you from?",
        "answer": "armenia"
      },
      {
        "question": "How satisfied were you with the product from 1 to 5 (5 = very satisfied)?",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you use the product for?",
        "answer": "to help me study"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you like most about it?",
        "answer": "ease of use"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you not you like about it?",
        "answer": "price"
      },
      {
        "question": "What would you improve or change?",
        "answer": "increase number of functions"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where were you when you used the product?",
        "answer": "at home"
      },
      {
        "question": "Was anyone else involved in the decision or experience?",
        "answer": "no"
      },
      {
        "question": "How did you first hear about this product?",
        "answer": "friend"
      }
    ],
    "analysis": "The interview responses indicate that the interviewee is a female named Milena Avagyan. She is of Asian ethnicity and was born on 07/02/2003. She is from Armenia. She rated her satisfaction with the product as 4 out of 5, meaning she was rather satisfied with it. Milena used the product to help her study and liked its ease of use the most. However, she was not satisfied with its price. If given the chance to improve or change something about the product, she would like to increase its number of functions. She used the product at home and there was no one else involved in her decision or experience using the product. She first heard about the product from a friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 1747143789944,
    "timestamp": "2025-05-13T13:43:09.944Z",
    "responses": [
      {
        "question": "What is your first and last name?",
        "answer": "ana smith"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your date of birth? (mm/dd/yyyy)",
        "answer": "08/09/2001"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your ethnicity?",
        "answer": "White"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "answer": "Female"
      },
      {
        "question": "What country are you from?",
        "answer": "US"
      },
      {
        "question": "How satisfied were you with the product from 1 to 5 (5 = very satisfied)?",
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you use the product for?",
        "answer": "essay writing"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you like most about it?",
        "answer": "nothing"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did you not you like about it?",
        "answer": "very complicated and messy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What would you improve or change?",
        "answer": "make it more structured"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where were you when you used the product?",
        "answer": "in university"
      },
      {
        "question": "Was anyone else involved in the decision or experience?",
        "answer": "my friends"
      },
      {
        "question": "How did you first hear about this product?",
        "answer": "from my sister"
      }
    ]
  }
]